internetmodeling.com 2019-04-21

# InternetModeling.com - Webcam Modeling Privacy Policy

## Webcam Model Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

Internet Modeling (herein "we", "us" or "Internet Modeling") has adopted this privacy policy to protect your personal information and to let you know how we might use it. This Privacy Policy only applies to activities you perform as a webcam model on the Internet Modeling website network, and activities or communications that occur while you are using the Internet Modeling website (collectively known as "our website") and does not apply to any other website or offline point of contact between Internet Modeling or any other company, and consumers. This policy was implemented on February 17, 2003 this policy may change from time-to-time, please periodically review this page. Each time you use our website or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.

### Your IP Address

### 

Like most websites, each time you use our website, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize our website for you and to diagnose problems, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. 

### Use Of Cookies

Like most websites, our website uses cookies to keep track of your activities on our website to enhance your experience. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal and financial information so you do not have to reenter it each time you use our website. Third party advertisers on our website may also place or read cookies on your browser. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain aspects of our website.

### Information We May Collect From You

In order to operate our website and to provide you with information about our services, such as providing _webcam jobs_ , recruiting webcam models, hiring webcam models, and other services that may be of interest to you, we may collect "personal information" (i.e. information that could be used to contact you directly without using our website), "demographic information" (i.e. information that you submit, or that we collect, that is neither personal information nor financial information which may include, but is not limited to, zip code, postal code, hometown, gender, username, age/birth date, browsing history information, [webcam model](http://www.internetmodeling.com/) or agent application history information, and **webcam model** or agent login history information), subject to the rest of this paragraph. Demographic information is divided into two categories: 1) "non-public information", which consists of browsing history information and one-on-one communications between you and agents of Internet Modeling; and 2) "public information", which consists of all other demographic information. We ask that you do not enter personal information or financial information into your "Profile" (for example, don't use your address or password as your username, or include your name or address in your public profile), because if you do then it may be posted publicly on our network, and the information will then be treated as "demographic information" that is "public information." Please note that nowhere on our website do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18, as we require that all users represent to us that they are at least 18 years old.

### Information Other Websites May Collect From You

On our website, we may place links to other websites operated by other parties. Some of these other websites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we may not control these other websites or these other websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other websites. Consequently, the operators of these other websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on our website. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

### How We Use Collected Personal Information

Internet Modeling is committed to treating your personal information with the highest degree of care. Your email address and personal information is not shared with any third parties and is solely used to send email communication from Internet Modeling. Your personal information will not be resold to any third party. We use your email address and your other personal information to help us efficiently operate our website, to contact you in connection with your modeling work with us and other activities on our website (including, but not limited to, confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with Internet Modeling). These types of communications are known as "Operational Communications.".

In order to support your **webcam modeling** activities with us, we may share your personal information with our direct agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as processing of your earnings payments, technical support services, and other relationship management services. We require these entities not to use your information for any other purpose. In no event do we ever share your personal information with end users of your performances on our network.

Any third party with whom we are allowed to share your personal information is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions.

### Changing our Privacy Policy for Previously Gathered Information

If at any point we decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or by providing 30 days notice on our website. Please note that we will continue to have the right to change our privacy policy and practices, and how we use your personally identifiable information, without notice, as described in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy, provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the change.
